아니면 머스타드 크립토나이트로 바꿔서
Or it turned into mustard Kryptonite,
지구를 위협하는 크립토니안 핫도그 변형체를 없애는 거야
the only way to destroy a rogue Kryptonian hotdog threatening Earth.
라지, 진지한 얘기 중이잖아
Raj, please, let's stay serious here.
슈퍼맨의 몸도 크립토니안이니까 땀도 크립토니안이야
Superman's body is Kryptonian, therefore his sweat is Kryptonian.
겨드랑이에 땀 자국은 어쩔 거야?
What about Kryptonian pit stains?
슈퍼맨은 지구에서 땀을 안 흘려
Superman doesn't sweat on Earth.
칸도르에 저녁 초대를 받고 가게 되면
He's invited for dinner in the Bottle City of Kandor.
몸을 축소할 테고, 칸도르에 들어가서는 초능력들을 쓸 수 없게 되겠지
He miniaturizes himself, enters the city where he loses his superpowers.
저녁을 먹기 전에 저녁 초대를 한 사람이 "공놀이 하실 분 계신가요?" 하고 묻자
Now, before dinner, his host says, "Who's up for a little Kryptonian tetherball?"
슈퍼맨이 땀 흘리면서 운동한 다음
Superman says "Sure," works up a sweat, comes back to Earth,